I I absolutely believe software
development is here to stay I think
coding is a different question and I
think it's Again part of that
exploration I I think what is software
development software development is
bringing ideas to life in the digital
world it's around creating something
that is either a repetitive task or it
is aggregating information and activity
that happens around or it is a creative
Outlet or just fun and all of these
things like there's no reason to think
that any of them go away so we would
still need to produce software I think
interesting things will happen to the
software development world but I think
other attributes like how do you build
software how do you maintain software
how do you collaborate around software I
think those will
change we have the advantage of only
changing them for the better in terms of
the ecosystem as a whole but it does
imply that some roles and some needs
will need to modify